2night.com 2012-12-29

# Privacy

Your privacy is extremely important to 2night.com, please read carefully the following Privacy Policy to understand our practices regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of information submitted to 2night.com Web site and Service (the "Service"). This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, the Terms of Service agreement, which governs your use of the Service.

**Information Collection**

• We collect user-submitted personal information, including name, and e-mail address.  
• We collect non-personal information including IP address and browser information.

**Information Use and Disclosure**

• We may display, and/or send targeted advertisements based on personal information submitted.

**E-mail choice / opt-out**

If you no longer wish to receive mailings from 2night.com, you may unsubscribe by clicking "Unsubscribe" link located at the bottom of our Newsletters.

**Use of cookies**

• We set and access 2night.com cookies on your computer.  
• Third-party advertisements may set and access cookies on your computer.

**Security**

• We take strong measures to protect the security of your personal information.  
• You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of the password and account.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. You can review the most current version at any time by clicking on the "Privacy Policy" link located at the bottom of our Web pages.

**Questions and Suggestions**

If you have any questions about your account or privacy, please contact us at privacy@2night.com
